[
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 257 - 132?",
    "answers": [
      "127",
      "124",
      "126",
      "125"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "125"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 7075?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "6",
      "9",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 20 \u00f7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 8900?",
    "answers": [
      "0",
      "1",
      "-1",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5141?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "3",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 1173?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "6",
      "7",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 624 + 617?",
    "answers": [
      "1243",
      "1241",
      "1240",
      "1242"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1241"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 213 - 117?",
    "answers": [
      "98",
      "97",
      "95",
      "96"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "96"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 779 + 147?",
    "answers": [
      "927",
      "925",
      "926",
      "928"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "926"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 959 + 407?",
    "answers": [
      "1368",
      "1366",
      "1365",
      "1367"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1366"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "71",
      "74",
      "72",
      "73"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "72"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 72 \u00f7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "13",
      "12",
      "14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3488?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "8",
      "10",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 149 + 689?",
    "answers": [
      "839",
      "840",
      "837",
      "838"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "838"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9 \u00f7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "3",
      "2",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "17",
      "14",
      "15",
      "16"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5749?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "6",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 36 \u00f7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "8",
      "11",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 351 - 102?",
    "answers": [
      "248",
      "249",
      "250",
      "251"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "249"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 478 + 214?",
    "answers": [
      "693",
      "691",
      "694",
      "692"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "692"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 700 + 142?",
    "answers": [
      "842",
      "843",
      "841",
      "844"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "842"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 96 \u00f7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "7",
      "10",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "18",
      "20",
      "17",
      "19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 99 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "10",
      "8",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 353 + 260?",
    "answers": [
      "612",
      "614",
      "615",
      "613"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "613"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 9548?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "6",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 684 + 571?",
    "answers": [
      "1256",
      "1255",
      "1254",
      "1257"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1255"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "23",
      "21",
      "22",
      "20"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "21"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 502 - 75?",
    "answers": [
      "428",
      "426",
      "427",
      "429"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "427"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 450 + 128?",
    "answers": [
      "579",
      "580",
      "578",
      "577"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "578"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 387 + 161?",
    "answers": [
      "550",
      "549",
      "547",
      "548"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "548"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "9",
      "8",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 867 - 184?",
    "answers": [
      "683",
      "682",
      "685",
      "684"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "683"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "132",
      "131",
      "133",
      "134"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "132"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 424 - 64?",
    "answers": [
      "359",
      "361",
      "360",
      "362"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "360"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "33",
      "32",
      "34",
      "31"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "32"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "5",
      "8",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 18 \u00f7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "5",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "40",
      "42",
      "39",
      "41"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "40"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "57",
      "55",
      "56",
      "54"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "55"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 366 + 702?",
    "answers": [
      "1067",
      "1070",
      "1069",
      "1068"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1068"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 805 + 953?",
    "answers": [
      "1759",
      "1758",
      "1757",
      "1760"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1758"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 408 + 327?",
    "answers": [
      "736",
      "735",
      "737",
      "734"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "735"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 421 + 883?",
    "answers": [
      "1304",
      "1303",
      "1305",
      "1306"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1304"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 922 + 693?",
    "answers": [
      "1616",
      "1617",
      "1614",
      "1615"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1615"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 905 + 408?",
    "answers": [
      "1314",
      "1312",
      "1313",
      "1315"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1313"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "18",
      "19",
      "20",
      "17"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "31",
      "34",
      "33",
      "32"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "32"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 81 \u00f7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "10",
      "8",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "49",
      "50",
      "48",
      "47"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "48"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 4052?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "7",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "6",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 7452?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "7",
      "6",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 795 - 58?",
    "answers": [
      "736",
      "739",
      "737",
      "738"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "737"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 7259?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "6",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "21",
      "20",
      "22",
      "19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 717 + 649?",
    "answers": [
      "1366",
      "1368",
      "1367",
      "1365"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1366"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 148 + 329?",
    "answers": [
      "477",
      "476",
      "479",
      "478"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "477"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 822 - 68?",
    "answers": [
      "756",
      "754",
      "755",
      "753"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "754"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "2",
      "1",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "8",
      "5",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 8700?",
    "answers": [
      "0",
      "-1",
      "2",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 742 - 168?",
    "answers": [
      "576",
      "573",
      "575",
      "574"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "574"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 974 + 389?",
    "answers": [
      "1365",
      "1364",
      "1362",
      "1363"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1363"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "13",
      "12",
      "14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 289 + 202?",
    "answers": [
      "490",
      "493",
      "491",
      "492"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "491"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "29",
      "31",
      "30",
      "32"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "30"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 664 - 88?",
    "answers": [
      "577",
      "576",
      "575",
      "578"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "576"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 36 \u00f7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "5",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 970 + 447?",
    "answers": [
      "1419",
      "1417",
      "1416",
      "1418"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1417"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 6476?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "7",
      "6",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "4",
      "3",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 22 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "1",
      "3",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "42",
      "40",
      "41",
      "39"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "40"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 347 + 516?",
    "answers": [
      "864",
      "865",
      "863",
      "862"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "863"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 194 + 983?",
    "answers": [
      "1179",
      "1178",
      "1176",
      "1177"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1177"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 20 \u00f7 2?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "9",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 929 - 61?",
    "answers": [
      "869",
      "870",
      "868",
      "867"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "868"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 9192?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "11",
      "10",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "5",
      "8",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 8858?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "7",
      "6",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 40 \u00f7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "4",
      "7",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 44 \u00f7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "13",
      "12",
      "10",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 48 \u00f7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "7",
      "10",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 513 - 142?",
    "answers": [
      "373",
      "372",
      "370",
      "371"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "371"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 9631?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "2",
      "4",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "8",
      "6",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 943 + 567?",
    "answers": [
      "1511",
      "1509",
      "1510",
      "1512"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1510"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 120 \u00f7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "13",
      "14",
      "11",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 156 + 979?",
    "answers": [
      "1136",
      "1137",
      "1135",
      "1134"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1135"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 4881?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "9",
      "8",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 28 \u00f7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "5",
      "4",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 48 \u00f7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "13",
      "12",
      "11",
      "14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 30 \u00f7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "7",
      "6",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 2554?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 8806?",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "-1",
      "0"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3779?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "9",
      "8",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 152 + 670?",
    "answers": [
      "822",
      "824",
      "823",
      "821"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "822"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "13",
      "14",
      "11",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 293 + 212?",
    "answers": [
      "506",
      "507",
      "504",
      "505"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "505"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 699 + 664?",
    "answers": [
      "1365",
      "1364",
      "1363",
      "1362"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1363"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 526 - 89?",
    "answers": [
      "436",
      "437",
      "438",
      "439"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "437"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3468?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "7",
      "8",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5165?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "5",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 260 - 120?",
    "answers": [
      "139",
      "141",
      "142",
      "140"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "140"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 54 \u00f7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "7",
      "8",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "5",
      "4",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 386 - 130?",
    "answers": [
      "256",
      "257",
      "258",
      "255"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "256"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "61",
      "60",
      "59",
      "62"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "60"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 808 + 132?",
    "answers": [
      "939",
      "942",
      "941",
      "940"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "940"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "8",
      "6",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5624?",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "4",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "17",
      "15",
      "16",
      "14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 96 \u00f7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "8",
      "9",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 1329?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "1",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "14",
      "12",
      "11",
      "13"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 940 - 149?",
    "answers": [
      "790",
      "792",
      "793",
      "791"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "791"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "42",
      "43",
      "41",
      "44"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "42"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 735 - 172?",
    "answers": [
      "565",
      "563",
      "564",
      "562"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "563"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3330?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "2",
      "5",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "119",
      "121",
      "120",
      "122"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "120"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "4",
      "3",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5014?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "0",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 476 - 189?",
    "answers": [
      "289",
      "288",
      "287",
      "286"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "287"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 72 \u00f7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "10",
      "9",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 72 \u00f7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "10",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 963 + 363?",
    "answers": [
      "1328",
      "1325",
      "1327",
      "1326"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1326"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 36 \u00f7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "13",
      "14",
      "11",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "26",
      "29",
      "27",
      "28"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "27"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "4",
      "6",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "36",
      "38",
      "37",
      "35"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "36"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 987 - 82?",
    "answers": [
      "905",
      "904",
      "906",
      "907"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "905"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "8",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 638 + 361?",
    "answers": [
      "999",
      "1001",
      "1000",
      "998"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "999"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 84 \u00f7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "13",
      "14",
      "12",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "86",
      "85",
      "83",
      "84"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "84"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 178 + 703?",
    "answers": [
      "883",
      "880",
      "881",
      "882"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "881"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 2385?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "7",
      "8",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "66",
      "67",
      "68",
      "65"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "66"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "85",
      "86",
      "83",
      "84"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "84"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "77",
      "78",
      "76",
      "79"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "77"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 9338?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "2",
      "3",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "31",
      "29",
      "30",
      "32"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "30"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4 \u00f7 2?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "1",
      "2",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "46",
      "44",
      "43",
      "45"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "44"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3180?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "10",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 80 \u00f7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "12",
      "11",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 571 + 333?",
    "answers": [
      "905",
      "904",
      "906",
      "903"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "904"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 72 \u00f7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "8",
      "5",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 1928?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "4",
      "3",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "50",
      "49",
      "52",
      "51"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "50"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "4",
      "5",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 323 + 274?",
    "answers": [
      "596",
      "597",
      "599",
      "598"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "597"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 550 - 178?",
    "answers": [
      "374",
      "372",
      "371",
      "373"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "372"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 653 + 617?",
    "answers": [
      "1269",
      "1272",
      "1270",
      "1271"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1270"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 42 \u00f7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "7",
      "8",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 422 + 487?",
    "answers": [
      "908",
      "911",
      "910",
      "909"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "909"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 45 \u00f7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "9",
      "11",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 195 + 894?",
    "answers": [
      "1090",
      "1089",
      "1088",
      "1091"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1089"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 772 - 96?",
    "answers": [
      "675",
      "678",
      "677",
      "676"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "676"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 794 + 427?",
    "answers": [
      "1223",
      "1220",
      "1221",
      "1222"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1221"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "1",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 783 + 616?",
    "answers": [
      "1399",
      "1401",
      "1400",
      "1398"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1399"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "2",
      "3",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "34",
      "32",
      "31",
      "33"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "32"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "17",
      "19",
      "18",
      "20"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "73",
      "74",
      "72",
      "71"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "72"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 27 \u00f7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "8",
      "9",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 484 - 100?",
    "answers": [
      "383",
      "384",
      "386",
      "385"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "384"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "3",
      "1",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "29",
      "30",
      "32",
      "31"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "30"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "60",
      "59",
      "62",
      "61"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "60"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 697 + 211?",
    "answers": [
      "909",
      "910",
      "908",
      "907"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "908"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "6",
      "3",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "39",
      "41",
      "40",
      "42"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "40"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 77 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "7",
      "6",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 197 + 708?",
    "answers": [
      "905",
      "907",
      "906",
      "904"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "905"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 88 \u00f7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "12",
      "13",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5014?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "1",
      "0",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "5",
      "8",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "4",
      "3",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 774 - 185?",
    "answers": [
      "589",
      "588",
      "590",
      "591"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "589"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "43",
      "42",
      "41",
      "44"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "42"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 36 \u00f7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "8",
      "9",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 468 + 230?",
    "answers": [
      "698",
      "700",
      "697",
      "699"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "698"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 580 + 607?",
    "answers": [
      "1187",
      "1189",
      "1188",
      "1186"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1187"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "9",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 525 + 228?",
    "answers": [
      "752",
      "753",
      "755",
      "754"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "753"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 243 + 514?",
    "answers": [
      "756",
      "759",
      "757",
      "758"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "757"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 634 + 434?",
    "answers": [
      "1069",
      "1067",
      "1070",
      "1068"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1068"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "4",
      "3",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "2",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 569 - 73?",
    "answers": [
      "497",
      "496",
      "495",
      "498"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "496"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "10",
      "7",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5332?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "4",
      "3",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 760 - 121?",
    "answers": [
      "639",
      "641",
      "638",
      "640"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "639"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 24 \u00f7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "4",
      "3",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 33 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "2",
      "5",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 956 - 197?",
    "answers": [
      "761",
      "759",
      "760",
      "758"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "759"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "37",
      "38",
      "36",
      "35"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "36"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 804 - 189?",
    "answers": [
      "615",
      "616",
      "614",
      "617"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "615"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 99 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "9",
      "10",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 663 + 824?",
    "answers": [
      "1489",
      "1486",
      "1487",
      "1488"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1487"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 32 \u00f7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "10",
      "7",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 808 - 146?",
    "answers": [
      "661",
      "664",
      "662",
      "663"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "662"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "7",
      "5",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 9531?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 633 - 144?",
    "answers": [
      "488",
      "490",
      "489",
      "491"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "489"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "55",
      "54",
      "57",
      "56"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "55"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 714 - 168?",
    "answers": [
      "546",
      "548",
      "545",
      "547"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "546"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 482 - 133?",
    "answers": [
      "350",
      "351",
      "348",
      "349"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "349"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 567 - 191?",
    "answers": [
      "377",
      "375",
      "376",
      "378"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "376"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "21",
      "20",
      "22",
      "19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 264 - 166?",
    "answers": [
      "97",
      "98",
      "99",
      "100"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "98"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 385 + 892?",
    "answers": [
      "1276",
      "1279",
      "1278",
      "1277"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1277"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 485 - 66?",
    "answers": [
      "419",
      "421",
      "418",
      "420"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "419"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "16",
      "18",
      "15",
      "17"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 602 - 170?",
    "answers": [
      "434",
      "433",
      "431",
      "432"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "432"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 2551?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "4",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "121",
      "120",
      "119",
      "122"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "120"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 \u00f7 2?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "4",
      "5",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 997 - 150?",
    "answers": [
      "848",
      "849",
      "846",
      "847"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "847"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 236 - 111?",
    "answers": [
      "127",
      "125",
      "126",
      "124"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "125"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "37",
      "35",
      "34",
      "36"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "35"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "7",
      "10",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 441 + 723?",
    "answers": [
      "1166",
      "1164",
      "1165",
      "1163"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1164"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 1130?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "5",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 726 - 151?",
    "answers": [
      "574",
      "575",
      "577",
      "576"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "575"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 225 - 188?",
    "answers": [
      "39",
      "36",
      "38",
      "37"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "37"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 20 \u00f7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "7",
      "4",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "7",
      "5",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3442?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "4",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 56 \u00f7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "10",
      "8",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 8953?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "5",
      "6",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "80",
      "82",
      "79",
      "81"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "80"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 224 + 299?",
    "answers": [
      "522",
      "523",
      "524",
      "525"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "523"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 18 \u00f7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "3",
      "2",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "64",
      "66",
      "63",
      "65"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "64"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "5",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 8538?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "3",
      "2",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5662?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "5",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 599 - 106?",
    "answers": [
      "493",
      "495",
      "494",
      "492"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "493"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 4505?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "1",
      "0",
      "-1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 260 - 195?",
    "answers": [
      "65",
      "64",
      "66",
      "67"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "65"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 713 - 104?",
    "answers": [
      "610",
      "608",
      "609",
      "611"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "609"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 6595?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "8",
      "9",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "90",
      "87",
      "88",
      "89"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "88"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 845 - 81?",
    "answers": [
      "763",
      "764",
      "765",
      "766"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "764"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "67",
      "65",
      "66",
      "68"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "66"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "18",
      "16",
      "17",
      "15"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 6614?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "0",
      "3",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 2558?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "6",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "132",
      "134",
      "133",
      "131"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "132"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 2468?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "8",
      "6",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 7166?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "6",
      "8",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "92",
      "89",
      "91",
      "90"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "90"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 7899?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "8",
      "10",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "71",
      "70",
      "72",
      "69"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "70"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 120 \u00f7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "9",
      "10",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 799 + 232?",
    "answers": [
      "1032",
      "1031",
      "1030",
      "1033"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1031"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 918 - 91?",
    "answers": [
      "827",
      "829",
      "826",
      "828"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "827"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 570 - 64?",
    "answers": [
      "508",
      "507",
      "506",
      "505"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "506"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 492 + 731?",
    "answers": [
      "1224",
      "1225",
      "1222",
      "1223"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1223"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 566 - 117?",
    "answers": [
      "450",
      "448",
      "449",
      "451"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "449"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 72 \u00f7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "9",
      "10",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 648 - 199?",
    "answers": [
      "448",
      "450",
      "451",
      "449"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "449"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3585?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "7",
      "10",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "98",
      "99",
      "100",
      "101"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "99"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 90 \u00f7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "9",
      "12",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 2892?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "8",
      "11",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 640 - 58?",
    "answers": [
      "582",
      "584",
      "583",
      "581"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "582"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "30",
      "29",
      "27",
      "28"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "28"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "73",
      "71",
      "72",
      "74"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "72"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "1",
      "2",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 408 - 110?",
    "answers": [
      "298",
      "300",
      "299",
      "297"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "298"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "6",
      "7",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "10",
      "8",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 544 - 52?",
    "answers": [
      "493",
      "491",
      "494",
      "492"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "492"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 24 \u00f7 2?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "12",
      "13",
      "14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "41",
      "39",
      "42",
      "40"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "40"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 806 - 178?",
    "answers": [
      "628",
      "627",
      "630",
      "629"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "628"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 256 - 75?",
    "answers": [
      "183",
      "181",
      "182",
      "180"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "181"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 960 - 167?",
    "answers": [
      "793",
      "792",
      "794",
      "795"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "793"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "11",
      "9",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "12",
      "14",
      "11",
      "13"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3391?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "11",
      "10",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "134",
      "131",
      "132",
      "133"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "132"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "6",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 561 + 618?",
    "answers": [
      "1178",
      "1179",
      "1181",
      "1180"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1179"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 2301?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "-1",
      "0",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 4412?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "0",
      "1",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 2196?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "8",
      "10",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 642 + 799?",
    "answers": [
      "1440",
      "1441",
      "1442",
      "1443"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1441"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "14",
      "13",
      "12",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00f7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "8",
      "7",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5451?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "16",
      "18",
      "15",
      "17"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "23",
      "21",
      "22",
      "20"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "21"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 510 + 426?",
    "answers": [
      "935",
      "938",
      "936",
      "937"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "936"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "29",
      "26",
      "27",
      "28"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "27"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 562 - 148?",
    "answers": [
      "416",
      "413",
      "415",
      "414"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "414"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3701?",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "0",
      "-1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 573 + 300?",
    "answers": [
      "874",
      "872",
      "875",
      "873"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "873"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 1528?",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "3",
      "4",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 437 - 107?",
    "answers": [
      "331",
      "332",
      "329",
      "330"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "330"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5047?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "35",
      "37",
      "34",
      "36"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "35"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 618 + 652?",
    "answers": [
      "1272",
      "1270",
      "1269",
      "1271"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1270"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "3",
      "5",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 499 + 990?",
    "answers": [
      "1489",
      "1491",
      "1490",
      "1488"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1489"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 838 + 597?",
    "answers": [
      "1437",
      "1436",
      "1434",
      "1435"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1435"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 8876?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "6",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 214 - 73?",
    "answers": [
      "140",
      "142",
      "143",
      "141"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "141"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "41",
      "42",
      "40",
      "39"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "40"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 556 + 225?",
    "answers": [
      "783",
      "780",
      "781",
      "782"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "781"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 591 - 192?",
    "answers": [
      "401",
      "398",
      "400",
      "399"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "399"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 1781?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "9",
      "7",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 132 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "13",
      "14",
      "11",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 380 + 474?",
    "answers": [
      "853",
      "856",
      "854",
      "855"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "854"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "8",
      "9",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 614 + 841?",
    "answers": [
      "1457",
      "1455",
      "1454",
      "1456"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1455"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 851 + 989?",
    "answers": [
      "1840",
      "1841",
      "1842",
      "1839"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1840"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 300 + 236?",
    "answers": [
      "537",
      "535",
      "536",
      "538"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "536"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "40",
      "41",
      "39",
      "42"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "40"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 72 \u00f7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "10",
      "9",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 606 - 67?",
    "answers": [
      "539",
      "541",
      "540",
      "538"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "539"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "26",
      "25",
      "23",
      "24"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5534?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 50 \u00f7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "10",
      "9",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5845?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "4",
      "3",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3511?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "0",
      "1",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 765 - 80?",
    "answers": [
      "685",
      "684",
      "687",
      "686"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "685"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 121 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "55",
      "54",
      "57",
      "56"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "55"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 9152?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "4",
      "7",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 40 \u00f7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "10",
      "8",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 7167?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "8",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "84",
      "83",
      "86",
      "85"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "84"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 35 \u00f7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "9",
      "7",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "35",
      "38",
      "36",
      "37"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "36"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "8",
      "11",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "80",
      "79",
      "81",
      "82"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "80"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 16 \u00f7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "1",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "100",
      "99",
      "101",
      "98"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "99"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 6446?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "6",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 475 - 71?",
    "answers": [
      "405",
      "403",
      "404",
      "406"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "404"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 2944?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "3",
      "5",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 77 \u00f7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "13",
      "10",
      "12",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 707 + 351?",
    "answers": [
      "1057",
      "1060",
      "1058",
      "1059"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1058"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "79",
      "77",
      "76",
      "78"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "77"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "29",
      "30",
      "32",
      "31"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "30"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 314 + 428?",
    "answers": [
      "742",
      "741",
      "744",
      "743"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "742"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "3",
      "2",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 16 \u00f7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "2",
      "1",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 121 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "12",
      "13",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 627 - 169?",
    "answers": [
      "459",
      "460",
      "457",
      "458"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "458"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "42",
      "40",
      "39",
      "41"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "40"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "50",
      "49",
      "51",
      "48"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "49"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 495 - 174?",
    "answers": [
      "323",
      "322",
      "320",
      "321"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "321"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 8081?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "9",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "9",
      "8",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 964 - 132?",
    "answers": [
      "832",
      "834",
      "831",
      "833"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "832"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 943 + 650?",
    "answers": [
      "1592",
      "1593",
      "1594",
      "1595"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1593"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 795 - 74?",
    "answers": [
      "723",
      "722",
      "720",
      "721"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "721"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 48 \u00f7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "12",
      "11",
      "13",
      "14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6 \u00f7 2?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "2",
      "5",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 870 + 108?",
    "answers": [
      "980",
      "977",
      "978",
      "979"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "978"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 842 + 550?",
    "answers": [
      "1392",
      "1391",
      "1393",
      "1394"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1392"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "49",
      "48",
      "50",
      "47"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "48"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 60 \u00f7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "6",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 827 - 187?",
    "answers": [
      "642",
      "639",
      "640",
      "641"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "640"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 665 + 779?",
    "answers": [
      "1444",
      "1446",
      "1443",
      "1445"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1444"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 571 - 105?",
    "answers": [
      "467",
      "466",
      "468",
      "465"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "466"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "6",
      "8",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 304 - 167?",
    "answers": [
      "136",
      "139",
      "138",
      "137"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "137"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 792 - 199?",
    "answers": [
      "593",
      "594",
      "592",
      "595"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "593"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00f7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "3",
      "4",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 33 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "2",
      "5",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 441 - 165?",
    "answers": [
      "276",
      "277",
      "275",
      "278"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "276"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "19",
      "17",
      "20",
      "18"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "6",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 404 - 98?",
    "answers": [
      "306",
      "305",
      "308",
      "307"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "306"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 921 - 168?",
    "answers": [
      "752",
      "754",
      "753",
      "755"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "753"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 44 \u00f7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "12",
      "11",
      "10",
      "13"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5473?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "6",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 847 + 405?",
    "answers": [
      "1254",
      "1251",
      "1252",
      "1253"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1252"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "9",
      "7",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 776 - 196?",
    "answers": [
      "581",
      "582",
      "579",
      "580"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "580"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 9069?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "7",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 772 - 84?",
    "answers": [
      "689",
      "688",
      "690",
      "687"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "688"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 60 \u00f7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "5",
      "8",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5694?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "10",
      "9",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 907 - 104?",
    "answers": [
      "803",
      "804",
      "805",
      "802"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "803"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "8",
      "7",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "31",
      "29",
      "30",
      "32"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "30"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 7574?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "6",
      "9",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "19",
      "17",
      "20",
      "18"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 18 \u00f7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "6",
      "5",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "2",
      "5",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "16",
      "15",
      "14",
      "17"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 472 - 80?",
    "answers": [
      "392",
      "394",
      "393",
      "391"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "392"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 24 \u00f7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "3",
      "6",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 14 \u00f7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "1",
      "4",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 612 + 924?",
    "answers": [
      "1538",
      "1536",
      "1535",
      "1537"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1536"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 924 + 232?",
    "answers": [
      "1156",
      "1158",
      "1155",
      "1157"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1156"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "9",
      "10",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9 \u00f7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "3",
      "2",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "10",
      "11",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 8057?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "7",
      "4",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "7",
      "6",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 499 - 155?",
    "answers": [
      "343",
      "345",
      "346",
      "344"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "344"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 566 + 255?",
    "answers": [
      "820",
      "823",
      "821",
      "822"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "821"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 404 + 654?",
    "answers": [
      "1060",
      "1058",
      "1057",
      "1059"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1058"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "6",
      "7",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 84 \u00f7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "6",
      "8",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 90 \u00f7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "8",
      "11",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 634 - 133?",
    "answers": [
      "500",
      "503",
      "502",
      "501"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "501"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 1932?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "4",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "85",
      "86",
      "83",
      "84"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "84"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 1784?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "9",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 63 \u00f7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "9",
      "8",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "63",
      "62",
      "65",
      "64"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "63"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 968 - 153?",
    "answers": [
      "815",
      "817",
      "814",
      "816"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "815"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "37",
      "36",
      "34",
      "35"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "35"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 724 + 672?",
    "answers": [
      "1397",
      "1398",
      "1396",
      "1395"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1396"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 9835?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "5",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "53",
      "54",
      "55",
      "56"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "54"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "5",
      "8",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 24 \u00f7 2?",
    "answers": [
      "14",
      "12",
      "11",
      "13"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 7639?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "4",
      "3",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 9568?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "6",
      "7",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "74",
      "72",
      "71",
      "73"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "72"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 9347?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "3",
      "6",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "121",
      "120",
      "122",
      "123"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "121"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 20 \u00f7 2?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "10",
      "9",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 961 + 587?",
    "answers": [
      "1547",
      "1548",
      "1550",
      "1549"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1548"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "5",
      "8",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 63 \u00f7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "7",
      "8",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 238 + 388?",
    "answers": [
      "628",
      "627",
      "626",
      "625"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "626"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "7",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 343 - 80?",
    "answers": [
      "265",
      "264",
      "262",
      "263"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "263"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 1721?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 2540?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "5",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "4",
      "5",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 2307?",
    "answers": [
      "0",
      "1",
      "-1",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 56 \u00f7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "10",
      "9",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 16 \u00f7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "1",
      "3",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 24 \u00f7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "3",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "17",
      "16",
      "14",
      "15"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 18 \u00f7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "5",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 7217?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "1",
      "0",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 810 + 274?",
    "answers": [
      "1086",
      "1085",
      "1083",
      "1084"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1084"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 508 - 170?",
    "answers": [
      "338",
      "337",
      "339",
      "340"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "338"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "62",
      "60",
      "61",
      "59"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "60"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "8",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 6525?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "4",
      "1",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 100 \u00f7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "12",
      "11",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "50",
      "51",
      "49",
      "52"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "50"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 1292?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "8",
      "10",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 568 - 115?",
    "answers": [
      "452",
      "454",
      "455",
      "453"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "453"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 32 \u00f7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "9",
      "8",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 45 \u00f7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "7",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 719 + 988?",
    "answers": [
      "1708",
      "1707",
      "1706",
      "1709"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1707"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 33 \u00f7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "10",
      "13",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 6597?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "9",
      "10",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "133",
      "131",
      "134",
      "132"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "132"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "111",
      "109",
      "110",
      "112"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "110"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 191 + 202?",
    "answers": [
      "393",
      "395",
      "394",
      "392"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "393"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "108",
      "110",
      "109",
      "107"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "108"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5756?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "4",
      "7",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "8",
      "5",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "8",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "47",
      "49",
      "50",
      "48"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "48"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "17",
      "19",
      "20",
      "18"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 489 + 713?",
    "answers": [
      "1201",
      "1204",
      "1203",
      "1202"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1202"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5022?",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "3",
      "4",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 646 + 795?",
    "answers": [
      "1443",
      "1441",
      "1440",
      "1442"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1441"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "20",
      "19",
      "22",
      "21"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "50",
      "48",
      "49",
      "51"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "49"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 705 + 398?",
    "answers": [
      "1104",
      "1105",
      "1102",
      "1103"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1103"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "6",
      "5",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 20 \u00f7 2?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "9",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "51",
      "50",
      "49",
      "52"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "50"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 24 \u00f7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "6",
      "5",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 646 + 717?",
    "answers": [
      "1365",
      "1364",
      "1362",
      "1363"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1363"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "8",
      "11",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "6",
      "5",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 737 - 179?",
    "answers": [
      "558",
      "559",
      "557",
      "560"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "558"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 497 + 896?",
    "answers": [
      "1393",
      "1395",
      "1392",
      "1394"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1393"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 366 - 136?",
    "answers": [
      "230",
      "231",
      "232",
      "229"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "230"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "6",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "108",
      "109",
      "107",
      "110"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "108"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 170 + 709?",
    "answers": [
      "878",
      "881",
      "880",
      "879"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "879"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 295 - 153?",
    "answers": [
      "144",
      "142",
      "143",
      "141"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "142"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 473 + 699?",
    "answers": [
      "1172",
      "1174",
      "1171",
      "1173"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1172"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "12",
      "11",
      "13",
      "14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 96 \u00f7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "9",
      "8",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 6998?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "10",
      "9",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 952 - 182?",
    "answers": [
      "769",
      "771",
      "772",
      "770"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "770"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 288 + 184?",
    "answers": [
      "473",
      "474",
      "472",
      "471"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "472"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 366 + 713?",
    "answers": [
      "1080",
      "1079",
      "1078",
      "1081"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1079"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "44",
      "43",
      "42",
      "41"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "42"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 128 + 749?",
    "answers": [
      "879",
      "876",
      "877",
      "878"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "877"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "28",
      "26",
      "27",
      "29"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "27"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 72 \u00f7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "14",
      "11",
      "13",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 27 \u00f7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "8",
      "9",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 509 + 616?",
    "answers": [
      "1126",
      "1125",
      "1124",
      "1127"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1125"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "101",
      "102",
      "99",
      "100"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "100"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "12",
      "14",
      "13"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "30",
      "27",
      "29",
      "28"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "28"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "17",
      "20",
      "19",
      "18"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 36 \u00f7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "11",
      "10",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 32 \u00f7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "4",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 310 - 99?",
    "answers": [
      "210",
      "213",
      "212",
      "211"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "211"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "32",
      "31",
      "29",
      "30"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "30"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "120",
      "119",
      "122",
      "121"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "120"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 941 - 108?",
    "answers": [
      "834",
      "832",
      "835",
      "833"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "833"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 672 - 147?",
    "answers": [
      "525",
      "527",
      "524",
      "526"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "525"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 560 - 76?",
    "answers": [
      "483",
      "484",
      "485",
      "486"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "484"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 66 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "5",
      "6",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 4638?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "2",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "102",
      "100",
      "99",
      "101"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "100"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 613 - 169?",
    "answers": [
      "444",
      "445",
      "443",
      "446"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "444"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 458 + 520?",
    "answers": [
      "980",
      "978",
      "977",
      "979"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "978"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 711 - 189?",
    "answers": [
      "521",
      "522",
      "524",
      "523"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "522"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "56",
      "54",
      "53",
      "55"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "54"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 433 - 137?",
    "answers": [
      "298",
      "295",
      "296",
      "297"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "296"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "9",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 269 - 68?",
    "answers": [
      "203",
      "201",
      "200",
      "202"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "201"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 60 \u00f7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "14",
      "12",
      "11",
      "13"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 824 - 59?",
    "answers": [
      "765",
      "766",
      "767",
      "764"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "765"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 40 \u00f7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "6",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "38",
      "36",
      "37",
      "35"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "36"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "4",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 110 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "11",
      "10",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 45 \u00f7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 18 \u00f7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "5",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 719 - 173?",
    "answers": [
      "546",
      "547",
      "545",
      "548"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "546"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 121 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "13",
      "12",
      "10",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 873 - 140?",
    "answers": [
      "735",
      "733",
      "732",
      "734"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "733"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 70 \u00f7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 7550?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "4",
      "5",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "43",
      "44",
      "46",
      "45"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "44"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 1076?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "8",
      "9",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 24 \u00f7 2?",
    "answers": [
      "13",
      "14",
      "12",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "25",
      "26",
      "24",
      "23"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 132 \u00f7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "12",
      "13",
      "11",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 604 - 101?",
    "answers": [
      "504",
      "502",
      "503",
      "505"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "503"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 8261?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "8",
      "7",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "47",
      "50",
      "49",
      "48"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "48"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "8",
      "11",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "18",
      "19",
      "20",
      "17"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "8",
      "5",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 44 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "3",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 579 + 803?",
    "answers": [
      "1382",
      "1383",
      "1381",
      "1384"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1382"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 596 - 107?",
    "answers": [
      "491",
      "490",
      "488",
      "489"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "489"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "14",
      "13",
      "11",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 598 + 303?",
    "answers": [
      "900",
      "902",
      "901",
      "903"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "901"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 16 \u00f7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "3",
      "2",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "14",
      "11",
      "13",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 982 - 102?",
    "answers": [
      "879",
      "881",
      "882",
      "880"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "880"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "11",
      "10",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 856 - 194?",
    "answers": [
      "663",
      "664",
      "661",
      "662"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "662"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 770 - 64?",
    "answers": [
      "705",
      "706",
      "707",
      "708"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "706"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 24 \u00f7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "2",
      "3",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 90 \u00f7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "8",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "72",
      "71",
      "70",
      "69"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "70"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 18 \u00f7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "4",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "5",
      "6",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "85",
      "84",
      "83",
      "86"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "84"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 203 - 195?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "7",
      "10",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 9979?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "6",
      "8",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3775?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "9",
      "7",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "6",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 450 + 262?",
    "answers": [
      "713",
      "711",
      "714",
      "712"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "712"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 8353?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 6131?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "2",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 443 + 387?",
    "answers": [
      "830",
      "831",
      "829",
      "832"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "830"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 7003?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "-1",
      "1",
      "0"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "57",
      "56",
      "54",
      "55"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "55"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "43",
      "42",
      "41",
      "44"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "42"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 632 - 138?",
    "answers": [
      "496",
      "495",
      "494",
      "493"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "494"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 50 \u00f7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "10",
      "12",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3744?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "3",
      "4",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 234 + 587?",
    "answers": [
      "821",
      "823",
      "822",
      "820"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "821"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "25",
      "23",
      "24",
      "26"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "12",
      "14",
      "13"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 27 \u00f7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "3",
      "2",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "8",
      "9",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "82",
      "80",
      "81",
      "83"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "81"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "7",
      "5",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 877 + 362?",
    "answers": [
      "1238",
      "1241",
      "1239",
      "1240"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1239"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "78",
      "79",
      "77",
      "76"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "77"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3497?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "9",
      "11",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 4186?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "10",
      "8",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "12",
      "13",
      "14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 353 + 957?",
    "answers": [
      "1312",
      "1310",
      "1311",
      "1309"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1310"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 2386?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "7",
      "10",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "14",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "35",
      "34",
      "33",
      "32"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "33"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 44 \u00f7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "13",
      "10",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "30",
      "29",
      "31",
      "32"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "30"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "7",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 60 \u00f7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "11",
      "10",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "16",
      "14",
      "17",
      "15"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 649 + 458?",
    "answers": [
      "1107",
      "1109",
      "1106",
      "1108"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1107"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 695 - 169?",
    "answers": [
      "527",
      "525",
      "526",
      "528"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "526"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5764?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "7",
      "5",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 107 + 382?",
    "answers": [
      "490",
      "491",
      "489",
      "488"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "489"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 221 + 126?",
    "answers": [
      "349",
      "348",
      "346",
      "347"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "347"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "31",
      "29",
      "32",
      "30"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "30"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 \u00f7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "1",
      "2",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "27",
      "30",
      "28",
      "29"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "28"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5468?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "7",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 387 + 594?",
    "answers": [
      "980",
      "981",
      "983",
      "982"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "981"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 663 - 142?",
    "answers": [
      "523",
      "522",
      "521",
      "520"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "521"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 120 \u00f7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "12",
      "11",
      "9",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 36 \u00f7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "6",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 36 \u00f7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 228 + 958?",
    "answers": [
      "1186",
      "1185",
      "1188",
      "1187"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1186"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 905 - 147?",
    "answers": [
      "757",
      "759",
      "760",
      "758"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "758"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3881?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "8",
      "9",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 1144?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "4",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "92",
      "89",
      "90",
      "91"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "90"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "52",
      "50",
      "51",
      "49"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "50"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 1717?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "1",
      "0",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 6862?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "8",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 819 + 254?",
    "answers": [
      "1073",
      "1072",
      "1075",
      "1074"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1073"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 709 - 125?",
    "answers": [
      "585",
      "586",
      "584",
      "583"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "584"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 226 + 557?",
    "answers": [
      "782",
      "783",
      "785",
      "784"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "783"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "7",
      "6",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 584 + 773?",
    "answers": [
      "1359",
      "1358",
      "1357",
      "1356"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1357"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "4",
      "3",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "56",
      "54",
      "53",
      "55"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "54"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 483 + 255?",
    "answers": [
      "739",
      "738",
      "737",
      "740"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "738"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 347 + 404?",
    "answers": [
      "751",
      "753",
      "750",
      "752"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "751"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "91",
      "89",
      "90",
      "92"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "90"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3842?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "6",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "6",
      "5",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 132 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "13",
      "12",
      "14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6 \u00f7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "4",
      "3",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 601 + 738?",
    "answers": [
      "1338",
      "1339",
      "1341",
      "1340"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1339"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 239 - 173?",
    "answers": [
      "67",
      "66",
      "68",
      "65"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "66"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "8",
      "10",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3942?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "5",
      "4",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "73",
      "71",
      "74",
      "72"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "72"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "73",
      "74",
      "72",
      "71"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "72"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "32",
      "31",
      "34",
      "33"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "32"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 842 + 156?",
    "answers": [
      "997",
      "999",
      "998",
      "1000"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "998"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "5",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 8804?",
    "answers": [
      "0",
      "2",
      "-1",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 7656?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "4",
      "7",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "87",
      "88",
      "89",
      "90"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "88"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 382 + 707?",
    "answers": [
      "1091",
      "1088",
      "1090",
      "1089"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1089"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 561 + 431?",
    "answers": [
      "993",
      "992",
      "994",
      "991"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "992"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "134",
      "132",
      "131",
      "133"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "132"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "8",
      "10",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 54 \u00f7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "5",
      "7",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3664?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "5",
      "6",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 630 - 145?",
    "answers": [
      "485",
      "484",
      "487",
      "486"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "485"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 \u00f7 2?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "6",
      "3",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 15 \u00f7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "7",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 208 + 799?",
    "answers": [
      "1009",
      "1006",
      "1008",
      "1007"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1007"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "3",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 338 + 588?",
    "answers": [
      "926",
      "928",
      "927",
      "925"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "926"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 353 - 80?",
    "answers": [
      "274",
      "275",
      "273",
      "272"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "273"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 786 - 103?",
    "answers": [
      "684",
      "683",
      "685",
      "682"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "683"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "90",
      "89",
      "88",
      "87"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "88"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 132 \u00f7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "12",
      "13",
      "11",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 28 \u00f7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "9",
      "8",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 701 + 755?",
    "answers": [
      "1455",
      "1456",
      "1457",
      "1458"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1456"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "4",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 48 \u00f7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "9",
      "10",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 697 - 72?",
    "answers": [
      "625",
      "624",
      "627",
      "626"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "625"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 984 - 175?",
    "answers": [
      "811",
      "808",
      "809",
      "810"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "809"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 8000?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "1",
      "0",
      "-1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "3",
      "6",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "5",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 953 - 81?",
    "answers": [
      "871",
      "872",
      "873",
      "874"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "872"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 6659?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "7",
      "5",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 24 \u00f7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "4",
      "3",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 6831?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "3",
      "2",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 641 - 182?",
    "answers": [
      "459",
      "461",
      "458",
      "460"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "459"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "121",
      "120",
      "119",
      "122"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "120"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "8",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 610 - 145?",
    "answers": [
      "466",
      "467",
      "465",
      "464"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "465"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "101",
      "100",
      "99",
      "98"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "99"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "10",
      "8",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 6905?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "0",
      "1",
      "-1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 350 - 108?",
    "answers": [
      "241",
      "242",
      "244",
      "243"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "242"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 406 - 125?",
    "answers": [
      "281",
      "282",
      "280",
      "283"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "281"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 22 \u00f7 2?",
    "answers": [
      "12",
      "13",
      "11",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 36 \u00f7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "13",
      "14",
      "11",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 229 - 56?",
    "answers": [
      "173",
      "174",
      "172",
      "175"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "173"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 710 + 807?",
    "answers": [
      "1517",
      "1519",
      "1516",
      "1518"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1517"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 551 - 195?",
    "answers": [
      "356",
      "355",
      "357",
      "358"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "356"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 164 + 378?",
    "answers": [
      "543",
      "542",
      "541",
      "544"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "542"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "122",
      "119",
      "121",
      "120"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "120"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "107",
      "109",
      "108",
      "110"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "108"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "86",
      "83",
      "85",
      "84"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "84"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "13",
      "11",
      "12",
      "14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 857 + 676?",
    "answers": [
      "1532",
      "1533",
      "1534",
      "1535"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1533"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "20",
      "18",
      "17",
      "19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 110 \u00f7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "13",
      "10",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 643 + 735?",
    "answers": [
      "1377",
      "1378",
      "1380",
      "1379"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1378"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 42 \u00f7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "8",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 108 \u00f7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "9",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 725 + 771?",
    "answers": [
      "1498",
      "1496",
      "1497",
      "1495"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1496"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "122",
      "120",
      "121",
      "123"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "121"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 108 \u00f7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "9",
      "10",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 164 + 694?",
    "answers": [
      "860",
      "858",
      "859",
      "857"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "858"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 332 + 705?",
    "answers": [
      "1039",
      "1036",
      "1037",
      "1038"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1037"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 372 - 119?",
    "answers": [
      "252",
      "254",
      "255",
      "253"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "253"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 713 - 57?",
    "answers": [
      "656",
      "657",
      "655",
      "658"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "656"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 587 + 257?",
    "answers": [
      "843",
      "845",
      "844",
      "846"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "844"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 122 + 797?",
    "answers": [
      "919",
      "918",
      "921",
      "920"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "919"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 535 + 845?",
    "answers": [
      "1379",
      "1381",
      "1380",
      "1382"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1380"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 781 + 923?",
    "answers": [
      "1706",
      "1703",
      "1705",
      "1704"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1704"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 60 \u00f7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "12",
      "13",
      "14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 235 + 621?",
    "answers": [
      "855",
      "857",
      "856",
      "858"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "856"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "7",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 8574?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "7",
      "9",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00f7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "1",
      "2",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00f7 2?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "5",
      "6",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 6979?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "8",
      "7",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 2444?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "3",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "62",
      "63",
      "65",
      "64"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "63"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "5",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "70",
      "71",
      "69",
      "72"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "70"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "8",
      "5",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 524 - 185?",
    "answers": [
      "340",
      "341",
      "338",
      "339"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "339"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 35 \u00f7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "5",
      "7",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 420 - 169?",
    "answers": [
      "251",
      "252",
      "250",
      "253"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "251"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "14",
      "17",
      "15",
      "16"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5413?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "0",
      "3",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 1949?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "3",
      "5",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 9708?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "-1",
      "0",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 500 - 177?",
    "answers": [
      "325",
      "322",
      "324",
      "323"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "323"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 50 \u00f7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "4",
      "7",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 209 - 175?",
    "answers": [
      "35",
      "33",
      "36",
      "34"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "34"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "7",
      "9",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "22",
      "21",
      "23",
      "20"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "21"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 654 + 592?",
    "answers": [
      "1246",
      "1247",
      "1245",
      "1248"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1246"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 4026?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "4",
      "1",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 485 - 108?",
    "answers": [
      "379",
      "377",
      "378",
      "376"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "377"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 701 + 252?",
    "answers": [
      "955",
      "953",
      "952",
      "954"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "953"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 80 \u00f7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "9",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "2",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 568 + 431?",
    "answers": [
      "999",
      "1001",
      "998",
      "1000"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "999"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 9960?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "8",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3642?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "6",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3341?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "4",
      "3",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "5",
      "6",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "10",
      "11",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 147 + 604?",
    "answers": [
      "753",
      "751",
      "752",
      "750"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "751"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 148 + 428?",
    "answers": [
      "575",
      "576",
      "577",
      "578"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "576"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 583 - 70?",
    "answers": [
      "512",
      "513",
      "515",
      "514"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "513"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 35 \u00f7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "6",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 877 - 99?",
    "answers": [
      "777",
      "778",
      "779",
      "780"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "778"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "2",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "3",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 581 - 76?",
    "answers": [
      "504",
      "506",
      "505",
      "507"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "505"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "50",
      "48",
      "47",
      "49"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "48"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 853 + 547?",
    "answers": [
      "1402",
      "1400",
      "1399",
      "1401"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1400"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "95",
      "98",
      "96",
      "97"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "96"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 531 + 511?",
    "answers": [
      "1041",
      "1042",
      "1043",
      "1044"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1042"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 22 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "131",
      "134",
      "132",
      "133"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "132"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 917 + 555?",
    "answers": [
      "1471",
      "1472",
      "1473",
      "1474"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1472"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 657 - 61?",
    "answers": [
      "595",
      "598",
      "596",
      "597"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "596"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "52",
      "49",
      "51",
      "50"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "50"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 33 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 60 \u00f7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "6",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 4062?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "7",
      "8",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 4827?",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "4",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3980?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "9",
      "10",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "7",
      "5",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 9702?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "1",
      "0",
      "-1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 2714?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "1",
      "0",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 895 - 74?",
    "answers": [
      "821",
      "820",
      "823",
      "822"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "821"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 961 + 575?",
    "answers": [
      "1536",
      "1538",
      "1537",
      "1535"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1536"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 2655?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "4",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5916?",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "0"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 654 - 168?",
    "answers": [
      "486",
      "487",
      "485",
      "488"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "486"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "80",
      "81",
      "79",
      "82"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "80"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 497 + 899?",
    "answers": [
      "1396",
      "1395",
      "1397",
      "1398"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1396"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "10",
      "8",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "14",
      "13",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "4",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "11",
      "9",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 22 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "4",
      "3",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "50",
      "49",
      "47",
      "48"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "48"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 637 + 633?",
    "answers": [
      "1270",
      "1272",
      "1269",
      "1271"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1270"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "62",
      "60",
      "59",
      "61"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "60"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 319 + 422?",
    "answers": [
      "742",
      "741",
      "740",
      "743"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "741"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 586 - 145?",
    "answers": [
      "442",
      "443",
      "440",
      "441"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "441"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 668 - 124?",
    "answers": [
      "545",
      "544",
      "546",
      "543"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "544"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "4",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 2095?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "11",
      "10",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 313 + 101?",
    "answers": [
      "416",
      "413",
      "415",
      "414"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "414"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "42",
      "40",
      "41",
      "39"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "40"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 658 - 173?",
    "answers": [
      "484",
      "487",
      "486",
      "485"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "485"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "96",
      "98",
      "97",
      "95"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "96"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 480 + 345?",
    "answers": [
      "827",
      "824",
      "825",
      "826"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "825"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "31",
      "30",
      "32",
      "29"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "30"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "45",
      "43",
      "46",
      "44"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "44"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 30 \u00f7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "6",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "7",
      "5",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 88 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "9",
      "7",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 28 \u00f7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "6",
      "3",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3773?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "7",
      "6",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 950 + 165?",
    "answers": [
      "1116",
      "1114",
      "1115",
      "1117"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1115"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 188 + 282?",
    "answers": [
      "469",
      "471",
      "470",
      "472"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "470"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 179 + 966?",
    "answers": [
      "1144",
      "1146",
      "1147",
      "1145"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1145"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 946 - 128?",
    "answers": [
      "819",
      "817",
      "818",
      "820"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "818"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 40 \u00f7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "9",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 517 - 97?",
    "answers": [
      "420",
      "421",
      "422",
      "419"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "420"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 18 \u00f7 2?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "10",
      "8",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "9",
      "10",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 478 + 542?",
    "answers": [
      "1019",
      "1020",
      "1022",
      "1021"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1020"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 974 + 500?",
    "answers": [
      "1474",
      "1475",
      "1476",
      "1473"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1474"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "29",
      "30",
      "27",
      "28"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "28"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "56",
      "58",
      "55",
      "57"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "56"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 24 \u00f7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "6",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 135 + 726?",
    "answers": [
      "863",
      "860",
      "862",
      "861"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "861"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 805 + 241?",
    "answers": [
      "1045",
      "1046",
      "1047",
      "1048"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1046"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 7852?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "4",
      "5",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 124 + 191?",
    "answers": [
      "314",
      "315",
      "316",
      "317"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "315"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 956 - 150?",
    "answers": [
      "808",
      "805",
      "806",
      "807"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "806"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 432 - 69?",
    "answers": [
      "364",
      "363",
      "365",
      "362"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "363"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 9629?",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "4",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3979?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "7",
      "9",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "18",
      "20",
      "17",
      "19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "79",
      "80",
      "82",
      "81"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "80"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 60 \u00f7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "7",
      "6",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 88 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "10",
      "7",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 54 \u00f7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "8",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "40",
      "39",
      "41",
      "42"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "40"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 334 - 160?",
    "answers": [
      "175",
      "173",
      "174",
      "176"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "174"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "3",
      "5",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 6996?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "8",
      "10",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 1423?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "3",
      "2",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 2338?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "2",
      "4",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 220 - 89?",
    "answers": [
      "133",
      "131",
      "130",
      "132"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "131"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 425 - 103?",
    "answers": [
      "324",
      "322",
      "321",
      "323"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "322"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "111",
      "109",
      "112",
      "110"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "110"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 368 - 80?",
    "answers": [
      "289",
      "288",
      "287",
      "290"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "288"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "72",
      "69",
      "71",
      "70"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "70"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 547 - 149?",
    "answers": [
      "398",
      "400",
      "397",
      "399"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "398"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 621 - 119?",
    "answers": [
      "504",
      "503",
      "502",
      "501"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "502"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 7648?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "3",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 8028?",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "4",
      "3",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 80 \u00f7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "10",
      "11",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 168 + 278?",
    "answers": [
      "448",
      "447",
      "446",
      "445"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "446"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 255 + 899?",
    "answers": [
      "1153",
      "1156",
      "1154",
      "1155"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1154"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00f7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "5",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "79",
      "78",
      "76",
      "77"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "77"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 945 - 137?",
    "answers": [
      "807",
      "810",
      "809",
      "808"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "808"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5844?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "6",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 397 - 135?",
    "answers": [
      "263",
      "262",
      "264",
      "261"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "262"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 595 + 149?",
    "answers": [
      "744",
      "745",
      "746",
      "743"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "744"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 703 + 968?",
    "answers": [
      "1671",
      "1670",
      "1673",
      "1672"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1671"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 204 - 66?",
    "answers": [
      "139",
      "140",
      "137",
      "138"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "138"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "4",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "5",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 706 - 112?",
    "answers": [
      "596",
      "595",
      "593",
      "594"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "594"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 990 - 165?",
    "answers": [
      "826",
      "824",
      "825",
      "827"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "825"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "19",
      "20",
      "17",
      "18"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 624 - 64?",
    "answers": [
      "559",
      "562",
      "560",
      "561"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "560"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "14",
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 44 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "6",
      "5",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "26",
      "24",
      "23",
      "25"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "7",
      "5",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 943 - 161?",
    "answers": [
      "783",
      "782",
      "781",
      "784"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "782"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 72 \u00f7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "12",
      "11",
      "13",
      "14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "144",
      "145",
      "143",
      "146"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "144"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "43",
      "42",
      "44",
      "41"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "42"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 990 - 51?",
    "answers": [
      "939",
      "938",
      "940",
      "941"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "939"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 72 \u00f7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "7",
      "8",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 757 + 344?",
    "answers": [
      "1103",
      "1101",
      "1102",
      "1100"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1101"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "34",
      "33",
      "32",
      "31"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "32"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "9",
      "8",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 821 - 111?",
    "answers": [
      "712",
      "709",
      "711",
      "710"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "710"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "8",
      "5",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "18",
      "19",
      "20",
      "17"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 983 - 97?",
    "answers": [
      "886",
      "885",
      "887",
      "888"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "886"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 90 \u00f7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "12",
      "9",
      "10",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 628 + 299?",
    "answers": [
      "926",
      "929",
      "927",
      "928"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "927"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 36 \u00f7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "9",
      "8",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3250?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "7",
      "5",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 21 \u00f7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "5",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 849 + 920?",
    "answers": [
      "1768",
      "1769",
      "1771",
      "1770"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1769"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 81 \u00f7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "9",
      "8",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "48",
      "47",
      "50",
      "49"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "48"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 96 \u00f7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "8",
      "10",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 973 + 188?",
    "answers": [
      "1161",
      "1160",
      "1163",
      "1162"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1161"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 680 - 66?",
    "answers": [
      "616",
      "615",
      "614",
      "613"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "614"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 959 - 176?",
    "answers": [
      "783",
      "784",
      "785",
      "782"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "783"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 15 \u00f7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "3",
      "4",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 33 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "5",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 404 + 989?",
    "answers": [
      "1394",
      "1395",
      "1393",
      "1392"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1393"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 365 + 990?",
    "answers": [
      "1354",
      "1357",
      "1355",
      "1356"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1355"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 28 \u00f7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "9",
      "8",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 268 - 100?",
    "answers": [
      "167",
      "169",
      "170",
      "168"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "168"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "90",
      "89",
      "92",
      "91"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "90"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "29",
      "30",
      "28",
      "27"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "28"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 88 \u00f7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "13",
      "10",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 726 - 144?",
    "answers": [
      "582",
      "581",
      "584",
      "583"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "582"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 2175?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "7",
      "8",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 132 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "13",
      "12",
      "14",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "26",
      "28",
      "27",
      "29"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "27"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 1921?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "2",
      "3",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 936 - 154?",
    "answers": [
      "782",
      "781",
      "783",
      "784"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "782"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "66",
      "68",
      "65",
      "67"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "66"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "29",
      "28",
      "26",
      "27"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "27"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "60",
      "62",
      "59",
      "61"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "60"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 84 \u00f7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "12",
      "13",
      "11",
      "14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "10",
      "9",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 77 \u00f7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "10",
      "13",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 424 - 198?",
    "answers": [
      "228",
      "227",
      "225",
      "226"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "226"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 986 + 327?",
    "answers": [
      "1312",
      "1314",
      "1315",
      "1313"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1313"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "9",
      "11",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "71",
      "72",
      "73",
      "74"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "72"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 7733?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "2",
      "4",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 234 - 78?",
    "answers": [
      "158",
      "156",
      "155",
      "157"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "156"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 7839?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "2",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 55 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "7",
      "6",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 163 + 977?",
    "answers": [
      "1139",
      "1141",
      "1140",
      "1142"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1140"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 7809?",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "0",
      "-1",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 12?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "5",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9 \u00d7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "100",
      "99",
      "101",
      "98"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "99"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 48 \u00f7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "12",
      "14",
      "13",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 119 + 870?",
    "answers": [
      "989",
      "988",
      "990",
      "991"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "989"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 9058?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "7",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 \u00d7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "80",
      "81",
      "79",
      "82"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "80"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 8051?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "7",
      "5",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 8960?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "5",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 977 + 112?",
    "answers": [
      "1090",
      "1089",
      "1091",
      "1088"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1089"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6 \u00f7 3?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "2",
      "1",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 9916?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "0",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "32",
      "34",
      "33",
      "31"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "32"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 749 + 359?",
    "answers": [
      "1107",
      "1110",
      "1109",
      "1108"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1108"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 921 - 51?",
    "answers": [
      "871",
      "872",
      "870",
      "869"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "870"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 77 \u00f7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "6",
      "9",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 383 - 168?",
    "answers": [
      "217",
      "216",
      "215",
      "214"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "215"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 9121?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "3",
      "2",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "38",
      "37",
      "36",
      "35"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "36"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 48 \u00f7 4?",
    "answers": [
      "13",
      "12",
      "11",
      "14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 668 + 726?",
    "answers": [
      "1395",
      "1393",
      "1394",
      "1396"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1394"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "69",
      "70",
      "71",
      "72"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "70"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 320 + 977?",
    "answers": [
      "1299",
      "1297",
      "1296",
      "1298"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1297"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 10 \u00d7 8?",
    "answers": [
      "81",
      "80",
      "82",
      "79"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "80"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5646?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "3",
      "5",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "6",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "7",
      "6",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 84 \u00f7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "7",
      "9",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "67",
      "66",
      "65",
      "68"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "66"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 775 + 889?",
    "answers": [
      "1666",
      "1665",
      "1663",
      "1664"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1664"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 70 \u00f7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "6",
      "8",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 430 + 602?",
    "answers": [
      "1034",
      "1031",
      "1033",
      "1032"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1032"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 9084?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "7",
      "10",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11 \u00d7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "56",
      "57",
      "54",
      "55"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "55"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 7877?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "8",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 4203?",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "-1",
      "0",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4 \u00d7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "49",
      "48",
      "50",
      "47"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "48"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 975 - 161?",
    "answers": [
      "813",
      "814",
      "816",
      "815"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "814"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 401 - 162?",
    "answers": [
      "239",
      "238",
      "240",
      "241"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "239"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 3715?",
    "answers": [
      "0",
      "1",
      "3",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 6829?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "2",
      "1",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "6",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 6?",
    "answers": [
      "43",
      "42",
      "44",
      "41"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "42"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 742 + 598?",
    "answers": [
      "1340",
      "1342",
      "1339",
      "1341"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1340"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "72",
      "70",
      "71",
      "69"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "70"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5371?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "6",
      "7",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 358 - 106?",
    "answers": [
      "252",
      "254",
      "253",
      "251"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "252"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 120 \u00f7 10?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "14",
      "13",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5 \u00d7 11?",
    "answers": [
      "54",
      "57",
      "56",
      "55"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "55"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 2846?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "3",
      "6",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 220 + 103?",
    "answers": [
      "325",
      "324",
      "323",
      "322"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "323"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 48 \u00f7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "6",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 \u00d7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "65",
      "64",
      "63",
      "62"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "63"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 35 \u00f7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "6",
      "7",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3 \u00d7 7?",
    "answers": [
      "20",
      "21",
      "23",
      "22"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "21"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "5",
      "8",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 24 \u00f7 12?",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "4",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12 \u00d7 5?",
    "answers": [
      "61",
      "59",
      "62",
      "60"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "60"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 of 36?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "9",
      "8",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 of 18?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "10",
      "8",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 6903?",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "0",
      "2",
      "-1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 2195?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "10",
      "11",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 of 24?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "3",
      "5",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 7703?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "-1",
      "1",
      "0"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6 \u00d7 9?",
    "answers": [
      "56",
      "54",
      "53",
      "55"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "54"
  },
  {
    "grade": 3,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the tens digit in 5738?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "4",
      "5",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  }
]